=Love Actually S5 Extra Episode=
What do you want to drink?
Want some yam water?
Give it a try.
Yam water.
Yeah, I went to a Chinese
medicine clinic yesterday
for acupuncture,
and they gave me this formula.
This can...
After coming back from Hainan,
we felt a bit damp-heat.
Drinking this can help
clear internal heat.
(Wellness)
And soothe our body gently.
(Wellness +1)
Have some.
It tastes plain,
but it works wonders for our health.
Xiaowen, want some?
(Wellness +2)
Okay, I'll have some.
I'll grab my cup.
It's hot.
What are you guys up to today?
If I don't finish my work soon,
my WeChat will blow up with messages.
You're busy with work today.
What about you?
I'm going to prepare
some farewell gifts for everyone.
It's hot.
Are you going to cook?
I'm going to make some food.
BK, haven't you eaten either?
Haven't you eaten either?
Meat swallow dumplings?
Breakfast?
No breakfast.
I just came down.
Make some together.
Hello.
Ruita.
Ruita looks so pretty today.
Your hair is sleek and smooth today.
Sleek hair.
He said the cake has been delivered.
(The cake ordered for Ji Yu)
It's at front gate. Want to go get it?
I'll go get it for you.
Let's go get it together.
You're so pretty today.
I bought a moth orchid for Ji Yu.
I looked up the meaning of moth orchids.
It represents happiness,
love, and beauty.
So impressive.
Yeah.
The gift itself doesn't matter much.
What matters is the meaning behind it.
He said it's placed at the...
Why can't I see it?
Is it at the other gate?
Really?
Probably.
This should be
the coffee bought by the rest of them.
Yang.
Yang Xihui.
Whatever, let's just take it first.
Let's go.
You are so nice!
So where's the other gate?
It is outside that hallway.
Put on your coat.
Okay.
It's a bit cold.
Coffee.
Hui's coffee.
Xiaowen, is it ready?
(Sous Chef on Duty)
It's ready.
Just toss it in.
No need to cover it.
No need.
Let's go. I'll get your coat.
This will do.
I'll just use this Pantene blanket.
No need to get it.
Help me put this on.
Let's go.
Time for this beauty to take a shower.
Going for a body scrub.
Is the body scrub master here today?
Not today.
They're all out on business trips.
I'm the only one here.
Would that work for you?
Unfortunately not.
We can't arrange a body scrub for you.
How about coming next time?
I'll book the attendant ahead for you.
Where should I put it?
Over here.
(Meat Swallow Dumplings ready)
Sauced Pork Wontons.
Pour it on.
Perfect.
Thanks for your hard work, Wentao.
It's okay.
Coming.
Are you sleeping?
No, I'm coming.
I look so messy.
Are you asleep?
I'm catching up on sleep.
Alright, go ahead and sleep.
Are you going out?
I might leave around three or four.
You look pretty handsome today.
Is it cold outside?
I don't know. I haven't been out yet.
It should be pretty cold.
Don't catch a cold.
You'll stay home, right? Not going out?
I stayed up too late.
Didn't have time to go out.
Okay.
Wait for me to come back, okay?
Don't leave.
Have some Qingbuliang
to line your stomach.
Okay.
Okay, go back to sleep.
Bye.
Hello.
I'm getting some hot water.
Have you eaten?
I had your meat patty.
Whose flowers are those?
BK gave them to me.
So happy.
We brought them from Beijing.
But I want to turn them
into dried flowers.
So I need to...
I need to...
Get something to press it, right?
You want to flatten them, right?
Yeah, tomorrow, I...
Once the sun comes out tomorrow,
it'll be fine.
When the sun is out,
you can start drying them.
Yes.
Let it sun-dry tomorrow.
I'll press them today.
What do you think about
going to Beijing with BK?
I think Beijing
changed my perception.
How so?
It became extremely beautiful.
Extremely beautiful?
Yeah.
Then it's actually about the person.
Indeed.
He makes every place lovely.
How was your trip to Xiamen?
It was good.
Just to experience
his daily life.
What did you think of his daily life?
I feel
I've seen another side of him.
He is extremely serious and dedicated
to his work.
Even though I haven't seen him at work,
I can sense it.
Also, meeting his friends.
I think Lizheng
sets high standards
and pursues excellence in his career.
Yeah.
Besides, he's on the rise.
So he'll spend a lot of energy
on work.
Yes.
So, have you talked about
the possibility of
a long-distance relationship later on?
Right now, both of us just want to
take things slow and get along.
Because we think life outside the house
will be different from
when we were inside.
So we just think...
It's more important
to spend time together first.
Right.
It's hard to tell for sure.
But I think you shouldn't overthink it.
There is no way
to know how things will turn out,
no matter how much we worry.
You can't really foresee it.
No matter how far you look ahead,
when you actually walk the path...
Things will shift.
Yeah.
I'll go upstairs
and sort out work matters.
Okay, go ahead.
You rest for a bit first.
Hard to wash them with such water.
Yeah, just leave it there.
It means
you need to rest.
My delivery is at the door.
Come with me to get it.
Okay.
I'll wrap a blanket around me
and head out.
I pressed the flowers a bit.
Take a look.
But you only pressed one page?
No.
I pressed in several places.
But this doesn't absorb water, right?
Press first.
Once flattened,
just let it dry out in the sun.
(Butt-powered flower pressing)
(Laughing my butt off)
(Butt that's all)
Do you want to put this on?
No.
Front door or back door? Back door?
Back door.
Need an umbrella?
The umbrella is also Pantene's.
Haven't you noticed?
You're really observant.
Yeah.
So what have you figured out?
I've found out
Ruita is my baby.
Really?
So wise.
Are you tired, baby?
I'm okay.
All yours.
Let's make two trips.
Okay?
Let's not be stubborn.
No, I'm just stubborn.
I'll take this.
I'll hold the umbrella.
Okay.
Then you do it.
You didn't get wet, did you?
Didn't get wet.
Thank you.
Besides, I'm fine today.
I don't mind getting wet.
I'm totally immune
and feel invincible right now.
Okay, let's go.
Let's run.
No need to run.
Are you comfortable like this?
Very comfortable.
Are you comfortable?
I'm comfortable.
Won't you run out of energy soon?
I'm full of energy.
Be careful.
It's fine, as long as my head
doesn't get bumped.
Alright.
Just leave it there.
Then let's cut the cake and eat it.
Let's cut it.
You make the first cut.
Okay.
Come on.
I really think Ji Yu
is like an astronaut.
How so?
He has his own pursuits.
He also has his own world.
May each of us
find our own planet.
Come on.
Give this to these two friends.
Okay?
Thank you.
Here, Xuan.
Thank you, Xuan.
Liu.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ji Yu.
Thank you, Ruita.
Come on.
Cheers with cake.
Cheers with cake. Come on.
Wish Ji Yu all the best.
Wish everyone keeps
getting better, okay?
All the best to everyone.
So happy to meet you all.
So happy to meet you.
So happy to meet everyone.
It's been many years
since anyone called me Ji Yu.
I'm so happy I can finally use my...
Real name online.
Yeah, to be my true self.
(30 minutes ago)
Should we take a group photo?
Come on.
Let me take a solo shot of you.
Okay.
So handsome.
Three, two, one.
Wentao and me.
Handsome!
Next one. Three, two, one.
Super handsome.
Too handsome!
All together, friends.
All together, hurry up.
Happy.
Wish Ji Yu finds his own planet.
Thank you.
Happy.
All these years, I have seldom
had so many
real friends beyond work.
We get together not for any gains,
simply because our personalities click.
They think I'm fun
and enjoyable,
so they want to be friends with me.
And they really hate to see me leave.
I could even
see
tears welling up in their eyes.
It's quite happy.
I think this is such a blessed feeling.
Because someone cares about you.
Someone values you.
It's quite precious.
In the house,
I didn't find the love I hoped for,
but I've gained a group of friends.
That's still incredibly precious.
We're here.
Let's go for a walk by the river first.
Great for a stroll.
It's a little sunny.
Do you want sunglasses?
I brought your sunglasses.
You brought my sunglasses?
The one you gave me.
The black and white one.
I thought I put it in my pocket.
Babe seems
to be a little forgetful.
I've put them away for you.
Okay.
Seems like
Liang is very organized.
My mom calls me Babe.
Babe.
So what does your mom call you?
My nickname is Liang.
Liang.
Unlike me, always losing things.
Here.
Pretty good.
Hello.
He might just
want to come say hi to you.
Really?
How do you know?
Because his eyes are all on you.
Do you like kids?
I like kids who aren't noisy.
Were you noisy as a kid?
Noisy.
What kid isn't noisy?
I wasn't.
Little boys are quite cute.
So little girls aren't cute?
Little girls...
As they grow up,
you have to worry about
so many things for them.
Little boys, on the other hand...
With little boys, there's not
nearly as much to worry about.
My mom said the same thing.
You were abroad
for seven years.
Did you miss home at first?
Only the beginning was tough.
It got better after a year.
When you missed home,
would you call them
and say you missed home?
Not really.
So you bottled everything up alone?
It seems we seldom speak of missing
in my family.
My brother might...
My brother might say to my mom,
"Mom, I miss you. Give me a hug."
But I wouldn't.
So you're not as good at
being affectionate
as your little brother.
Right.
Why?
When I was at the age
of being affectionate,
I wasn't around them.
So how did you cope with it?
I had friends.
I played games.
I had other emotional anchors.
But I read
in your profile that
(Stress brought me to tears late at night)
you sometimes cried quietly late at night.
That happened
back when I was in the UK,
whenever the stress piled up.
It wasn't really crying.
It was more like...
A way to release pressure
when it's high.
Sometimes when I'm showering,
I may reflect on what I didn't do well.
Simply letting off steam.
After showering
and looking in the mirror,
I'm still standing strong.
Then I'd feel better.
So I recover very fast.
I've got a huge health bar.
When I'm under a lot of pressure,
in the UK, I was like that too.
It happened very rarely.
I think only once or twice.
But those two times
left a deep impression on me.
I wondered...
It even made you cry?
It even made you cry.
You must be under
a lot of pressure lately.
Do you tell your parents?
No.
Do you take everything on alone?
Even if you tell them,
they can understand,
and give you some comfort,
but it's just comfort.
Instead, they...
Right?
Seeing a grown man
in tears,
consumed by anxiety.
So I don't really talk about it.
So in a relationship,
if you encounter similar pressure,
or things that don't go your way,
would you share it with your partner?
Do you want to listen?
If you want to listen, I can tell you.
I hope to be the thread
that can let you loose.
I mean, if there is,
I'll definitely tell you.
But I think normally,
there aren't many things
that can affect my mood.
Yeah, there isn't much.
I really think you don't have much
emotional fluctuation.
Not much.
Every day, just...
Take a selfie. Look.
Like this. Okay.
Like this?
Nice hairstyle.
A bit pretty.
Let's go.
Almost done?
Almost done.
Time to go home and cook!
Going home to cook for my baby.
Baby's meal.
Today it's crab roe burger.
(Zhou Youling and Xu Lvyang's
Real Life Trip)
Have you decided what to cook?
(Playing dumb)
You said yesterday you'd think about it?
I thought about mine.
I thought about beef.
In my domain.
I like it.
This floor is the point.
This smells amazing.
I feel like I could eat this
all by myself.
Really?
Really.
You can eat that much?
This one is also delicious.
We can add a vegetable.
This looks way too delicious.
This one is okay, I think.
This sauce is really tasty.
I can go for this.
I like this one.
Your favorite.
My favorite. I like it.
This is very tasty.
Which one?
This spicy cold beef. There's a lot.
This can be brought to the house.
This is my dad's favorite.
Really?
Really.
Every time he comes here,
he has to buy this.
What do you usually like to browse?
What categories?
Food.
(Nonsense)
Definitely food.
This box looks good and big.
Yes.
I feel like it looks very delicious.
Come on.
Will you eat it?
I'll eat it.
I need to make sure
someone will eat it with me.
I'll eat it. I eat any snack.
Oh no, I want to eat everything I see.
I also want to eat everything I see.
I should have come after eating.
(Miscalculated)
(It won't help)
Even if I come full, I still want to eat.
Almost done. Let's go.
(Heading to Zhou Youling's home)
Let's go.
So are we cooking here later?
Yes, cooking right here.
And stir-frying here.
Okay.
Prep over here.
Is this your mother?
Fat cat.
Yeah.
So pretty.
Yes.
These are Brother's parents.
It's a mixed breed, right?
Right.
Here.
This is Lanbo.
Lanbo.
At eleven years old.
Coming.
It wants to stand up.
Don't shake.
Why is it shaking?
Baby.
A bit excited.
Haven't seen you in a long time, right?
How long has it been since you saw it?
You, half a month.
Quite a while.
Just this past month.
Why is it shaking so much?
This month, I've only seen it once.
So pitiful.
An old man.
Excited.
Hello.
Okay.
Still shaking?
Not shaking anymore.
A little bit.
Good boy.
Come to see you.
Lanbo.
Do they fight?
No, the two of them...
Very harmonious.
They don't mess with each other.
They just ignore each other.
Let's go.
Let's wash our hands
and start preparing.
Blanch it, right?
Do you want to blanch it
or just boil it directly?
Blanch it.
Is it hot?
A little hot.
Very hot, isn't it?
Where did the gloves go?
Gloves matter.
Actually, it's okay.
You don't need to look for them.
Not hot.
Really?
They say girls aren't afraid of heat.
I'm really not afraid of heat.
Do we need to add anything else?
Should we add lemon?
Or after...
No need.
After it cools down.
It's almost done. Okay.
Then I'll turn it off.
Turn it off.
Don't grab
the two handles barehanded.
These handles are super-hot.
Okay.
Because this pot is small.
Then let it cool.
That sauce you made smells so good.
You really have some talent.
I just cooked it randomly.
One pot wonder.
Get some lemon.
The lemon is over there.
Maybe I should mix the cold noodles.
Sure.
You can blanch the shrimp.
Okay.
I think it's not sweet enough.
Did you put too much dark soy sauce?
It's
my taste.
Is it a bit salty?
A bit.
But if you reduce it further,
it'll get saltier.
Take it out.
Drizzle a little sauce.
(A little bit)
(Strictly enforced)
I smell the aroma.
We've made some.
You can eat first.
No need.
Well.
I can't.
(Just wanted to see)
Eating alone doesn't look right.
Almost ready.
It'll be ready at around seven o'clock.
Very soon.
This bowl is too small; I can't open it.
It goes to this position.
Let me show you.
Come on, take a look.
See it?
Okay, you're here.
You get ready first.
It smells so good.
Delicious.
And then? What about the rest?
Wait a moment.
Where's the rest?
You can come and serve yourselves later.
Is everything set up now?
I think so.
Just a little while longer.
Dinner will be ready soon.
You've cooked way too much.
Could
four people ever eat this much?
We can all just come and eat now.
Look at it.
I,
I forgot my own role.
I thought I was a staff member
and was going to hide along with them.
You're so humorous.
Let's eat.
Welcome.
Welcome to you.
You've worked hard today.
Not at all.
This is really well done.
Yes, this is very well-made.
As delicious as dishes
from a five-star hotel
(A long string)
You've given me too much.
Let's split it half and half.
Right.
It's just...
My knife skills aren't good enough.
The knife work.
Liu did the cutting.
Let's toast to the two of them.
Thank them
for making
such a lavish meal today.
Okay.
Liu,
thank you.
Thank you, Mr. and Mrs. Zhou.
You've worked hard.
And it was cooked really deliciously.
Time to head back.
You don't want to go back
to the house, do you?
Actually, it's okay.
I'm pretty okay with it.
I am...
Tell me, what are you?
I actually quite like
staying in the house.
What about you?
Like, to extend
your stay in the house for another week,
and to end it immediately,
which would you choose?
Extend for a week.
And you?
Me too.
Why?
Because you like living with friends.
That's one reason.
What else?
For example,
if it ends and we
to hang out,
it feels like it's different
from being there.
Why?
I don't know.
I feel like I'm setting a trap for you.
Yes.
I caught on.
It would be nice if there was
an ancient town this beautiful.
I think I know what you like now.
What?
That kind of antique and quaint style.
But I am, outwardly,
well, not just outwardly,
I feel that I don't
seem to like ancient times.
I look modern,
but I actually like ancient things.
It's about time to go back.
Okay.
You're living over there now.
Is
your life all normal?
You get up early?
Yes.
It's just fine.
If earlier,
we may get up around ten o'clock.
Because we finish late at night.
Usually we're up
until two or three in the morning.
Then they give us time to sleep
during the daytime.
Around two or three.
You guys must find it pretty tough.
Right? Our family is used to it.
In our family, we usually
don't sleep at two or three.
Do you usually sleep late?
Usually, I don't sleep late myself.
Don't sleep late.
Right, by myself, I don't sleep late.
It's a good habit, actually.
We got up late in Hainan.
Because it's hot
during the day in Hainan,
we can't do anything.
Usually, after three or four
in the afternoon,
we'd go out.
So basically, we might
get up at eleven or noon.
We stayed in Hainan
for quite a long time.
Quite long, seven days.
We first went to Sanya in 1988.
We got married on a trip
to Sanya.
We didn't hold a wedding banquet.
In that era...
It was very trendy.
We two had a travel wedding.
I took a photo of her.
It even won an award!
Yes.
If you have a chance
to come by in the future,
I'll show you.
The award-winning piece.
The photography talent
is also inherited.
Inherited from Mr. or Mrs. Zhou?
Me.
It's mainly inherited from me.
Of course, the good traits
are mostly from me.
His good points are all from him,
and the flaws are all from me.
How could that be?
Back then, the camera equipment
and the whole set for developing
and printing photos
were made by me.
He made it himself.
And developed the photos.
I made even the parts.
That's so impressive.
He is...
I am a senior technician.
Yes, senior technician.
We can go now.
You guys tidy up.
Is it about right?
We're leaving.
Don't leave anything behind.
I'm just afraid you'll forget something.
Every time he leaves,
he doesn't take his stuff.
He'll use an express delivery
(Mom's roast)
to pick up things again and again.
Even the dog can be sent
by express delivery.
How ridiculous.
Brother is scared when it is sent
by express delivery.
Then it's better to take our own car.
Even in our own car, it still shakes.
It's a little better.
Okay, you've worked hard.
Leave early.
Goodbye.
Okay, take care.
Take care. Get in the car first.
Go on.
Goodbye.
They're off.
Leaving you behind.
Leaving you behind again.
Xiaowen is taking a shower.
I don't know.
His room.
He's inside.
You look so handsome today.
I heard you lost.
I lost.
Yes, you look so handsome today.
Well, look at that.
So preppy.
You...
Why
did Xuan
tell everyone I lost
about this thing today?
Who actually lost?
I misjudged you.
She won.
I won one round; she won two.
I thought you could win completely.
It's just skill.
Last time, I didn't play seriously
against you.
Did you lose to him last time,
or what?
No.
Last time we didn't keep score.
But I feel like I can compete with her.
With whom? With her?
Are you going to help Xiaowen
get revenge?
How was it for you two today?
Why are you laughing?
Ask him.
Ask me what?
I feel great.
You are very...
You were brought there today,
so of course they should ask you.
I also feel pretty good.
How was it?
His parents...
Were you happy?
They were very nice people.
His parents were very nice people.
Let me show you the dishes I made today.
You made dishes?
He made a lot today.
You, a delivery order person, can cook?
Is this hotpot?
You can actually cook?
He's especially funny.
This is...
His dad said it was the first time ever.
This is the Huadiao wine
marinated sweet shrimp.
For you.
This is salmon
and black truffle fried rice.
This is garlic Wagyu and mushrooms.
Bro, when can I
get to eat these things?
It was super delicious.
Will you cook tomorrow?
I didn't get to eat it.
No, I just want to eat at this table.
(Tao also wants a seat at the table)
That's fine.
He will definitely invite you.
Yes.
It's a sure thing, right?
Coming to my house, isn't that
I just want to eat at this table.
So when you come to Shanghai
in the future,
you won't stay in a hotel.
Well, I think
I'll free up three or four months,
and I'll just
stay in Shanghai.
A long-term stay.
It's not a problem.
Whether it works out or not,
his mother will still like you.
Sweet.
She's at it again.
You two are really hilarious.
A thousand words turn
into a finger heart.